<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><search><entry><title>Support block information emphasis annotation in Markdown documents</title><url>/en-us/demo/hugo-blockquote.html</url><categories><category>Example</category><category>Grammar</category></categories><tags><tag>blockquote</tag><tag>Hugo</tag></tags><content type="html"><![CDATA[  In the past, the Hugo NexT theme used to annotate block information through custom phrases. Recently, it has been discovered that Hugo has been updated from v0.134.0 . From the beginning of the version, it is possible to support rendering Blockquote styles in Markdown documents through hook mode (which needs to be implemented by oneself), achieving warning style styles similar to Github. So 7 different styles were added to the Hugo NexT theme for users to choose from, and they could also customize icons and color configurations.
Users can find the positions of the following two configuration items and adjust them according to their preferred style and color:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 #Config. yaml or hugo.toml postAlerts: info: icon: &#34;circle-info&#34; color: &#34;#4A90E2&#34; note: icon: &#34;bell&#34; color: &#34;#17A2B8&#34; help: icon: &#34;circle-question&#34; color: &#34;#967ADC&#34; error: icon: &#34;circle-xmark&#34; color: &#34;#DC3545&#34; warning: icon: &#34;triangle-exclamation&#34; color: &#34;#F39C12&#34; success: icon: &#34;circle-check&#34; color: &#34;#32CD32&#34; important: icon: &#34;circle-plus&#34; color: &#34;#007BFF&#34; 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 # i18n/zh-cn.yaml PostAlert: info : Information note : Attention help : &#39;Help&#39; error : Error warning : Warning success : &#39;Success&#39; important: &#39;Important&#39; The writing style and specific implementation effects in the Maarkdown document are as follows:
Information prompt 1 2 &gt; [!INFO] &gt; HugoNexT theme supports custom style design, allowing you to achieve personalized design for your own site. Info HugoNexT theme supports custom style design, allowing you to achieve personalized design for your own site.
Attention to information 1 2 &gt; [!NOTE] &gt; The latest version of the `Hugo NexT` theme supports Blockquote rendering for Markdown documents, with 7 different styles to choose from or customize. Note The latest version of the Hugo NexT theme supports Blockquote rendering for Markdown documents, with 7 different styles to choose from or customize.
Help Information 1 2 &gt; [!HELP] &gt; The HugoNexT theme provides complete example usage instructions and source code, making it easier to get started and use. Help The HugoNexT theme provides complete example usage instructions and source code, making it easier to get started and use.
Warning message 1 2 &gt; [!WARNING] &gt; The HugoNexT theme uses SCSS precompilation and requires downloading the official Hugo extended version for use. Warning The HugoNexT theme uses SCSS precompilation and requires downloading the official Hugo extended version for use.
Error message 1 2 &gt; [!ERROR] &gt; The `Hugo NexT` theme is only supported in Hugo v0.132.0 and above versions. Error The Hugo NexT theme is only supported in Hugo v0.132.0 and above versions.
Success message 1 2 &gt; [!SUCCESS] &gt; Congratulations on successfully deploying the `Hugo NexT` theme. Please feel free to start your creative work. Success Congratulations on successfully deploying the Hugo NexT theme. Please feel free to start your creative work.
Important information 1 2 &gt; [!IMPORTANT] &gt; The HugoNexT theme supports the use of external CDN services, but please ensure that your network is functioning properly and accessible to CDN services at this time. Important The HugoNexT theme supports the use of external CDN services, but please ensure that your network is functioning properly and accessible to CDN services at this time.
Custom Title 1 2 &gt; [!Info]+Custom Title Description &gt; The HugoNexT theme provides very open and flexible configurations, allowing users to customize according to their own ideas. Custom Title Description The HugoNexT theme provides very open and flexible configurations, allowing users to customize according to their own ideas.
  ]]></content></entry><entry><title>About Hugo NexT Organization</title><url>/en-us/about.html</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html"><![CDATA[  The Hugo NexT organization is jointly established by numerous friends from around the world who are fond of the NexT theme and style. The aim is to continue promoting and enhancing this theme within the Hugo engine. We warmly welcome you to join us!
Our Vision Continuing the classic black-and-white color scheme of NexT, it maintains simple usability and powerful functionality.
Usage Feedback Join the online discussions on GitHub Discussions or Gitter &#x1f37b; GitHub Issues Submit a bug report &#x1f41b; GitHub Feature to propose new feature ideas &#x2728; Info Chinese&rsquo;s users can also join the QQ group for communication: 604710815
  ]]></content></entry><entry><title>Demo Sites</title><url>/en-us/flinks.html</url><categories/><tags/><content type="html">  If you want to exchange friendly links on this site, please leave your site information in the comment section. The format reference is as follows:
1 2 3 4 - name: Hugo-NexT desc: Hugo NexT Official Site. avatar: https://hugo-next.eu.org/imgs/hugo_next_avatar.png link: https://hugo-next.eu.org   </content></entry></search>